{
    "id": "0dc736511531455bb6ab8071b075307a",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "'I haven't turned in the assignment ‘………………………….. have I.’",
            "description": "After a negative remark, we can add another negative remark to it with neither or nor. ",
            "answers": [
                "So",
                "Neither",
                "Nor"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ........................... cute.",
            "description": "We do not use so much to modify adjectives and adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "so",
                "so much"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She worked hard so that she ................................. more.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will earn",
                "might earn",
                "can earn"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited for ........................... two hours and then I went home.",
            "description": "We can use another with plural expressions of quantity.",
            "answers": [
                "an other",
                "another",
                "other"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I call my mother ..............................",
            "description": "Everyday means ordinary or typical. Every day means each day.",
            "answers": [
                "everyday",
                "every day",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My ………………………………  too heavy.",
            "description": "Luggage does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "luggage is",
                "luggage are",
                "luggages are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Either Sam or Peter .............................. to bring the violin.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb when two singular nouns are connected by either/or. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I would rather you .................................... talking to her.",
            "description": "Use a past tense after would rather to refer to the future. ",
            "answers": [
                "stop",
                "stopped",
                "will stop"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "At least 10 people ................................... in the explosion.",
            "description": "A passive verb is required here. ",
            "answers": [
                "have killed",
                "had killed",
                "have been killed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "A number of people .................................. to migrate.",
            "description": "Use a plural verb after a number of use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "wants",
                "are wanting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of people who want to migrate ................................. on the rise.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after the number of.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}